https://www.stress.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy and Personal Data Protection Statement
Protecting your personal data is a priority to Stress Engineering Services, Inc. and its affiliates. This is the privacy and personal data protection statement of Stress Engineering Services, Inc. and its affiliates, which we may update from time to time. You may visit our website and browse without having to provide any personal data.
This privacy policy sets out how Stress Engineering Services, Inc. (hereafter referred to as “Stress Engineering,” “we,” or “us”) uses and protects any information that the user of this website (hereafter referred to as “you”) gives Stress Engineering when you use this website. Stress Engineering is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected.
Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Stress Engineering may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
Name and job title
Contact information including email address
Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
Information you post or provide when using this website
Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
Collection, use and disclosure of your personal data
The personal data we collect from you will be used in the following ways:
Provision of services to you: Where you have engaged us to provide services to you or your company, your personal data may be collected, used and disclosed by Stress Engineering and its affiliates, service providers and agents to enable Stress Engineering and its affiliates, service providers and agents to properly provide services to or for you, and to enable Stress Engineering and its affiliates, services providers and agents to comply with applicable laws, regulations, industry codes and guidelines, and for internal audit.
Request for contact: Where you provide information via the Contact Us page on our website or by any other method, your personal data may be used to contact you in response to your inquiry or to provide information regarding Stress Engineering Services, Inc. and its affiliates, including electronic publications (such as bulletins, updates, alerts, reviews, invitations and announcements), and we will use your personal data to send such publications to you.
Email marketing: We occasionally send email marketing materials to clients and future clients who have provided permission for the purposes of sharing industry information, news items from Stress Engineering and other relevant information from our company. You may unsubscribe at any time and we will remove you from our email marketing list. All requests to be unsubscribed from our email lists are strictly followed. To be removed from our marketing email list, contact us at privacy@stress.com.
Children
We do not direct any websites to, nor do we knowingly collect any personal information from children under 13.
International Users
If you are located outside of the United States, please be aware that your information will be transferred to, processed and stored in the United States and in other countries where we do business.
By submitting your personal data, you agree that we may transfer, process and store your data in this way. Wherever the data is, it will be treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and applicable privacy laws in North America and the EU.  These laws may be different from the privacy laws in your country. However, this does not change our commitments to safeguard your privacy and we will comply with all applicable laws relating to the cross-border data disclosure of your personal information.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online through the use of a variety of commercially reasonable, industry standard physical, administrative and technical safeguards.
The Internet, however, is not perfectly secure and we are not responsible for security incidents not reasonably foreseeable or reasonably within our control.
We require that you maintain the confidentiality of your user names and passwords. If you become aware of any unauthorized use of an account, loss of your account credentials or suspect a security breach, notify us immediately.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Notice to Job Applicants: Stress Engineering uses a third party to collect information from job applicants. This third party’s privacy policy shall apply to all use of their site. Stress Engineering disclaims all liability and shall not be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information disclosed on such third party’s site.
Controlling your personal information
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
Contact us
If you have any inquiries, comments or suggestions about our collection or use of your personal data or this statement, we would be pleased to receive them if you contact our Privacy and Data Protection Officer by email at privacy@stress.com or at Stress Engineering Services Inc., 13800 Westfair East Drive, Houston, Texas, 77041, USA.
If you would like to receive information about the personal data we have in relation to you, to update such personal data, to withdraw any consent you have provided to us previously or to be removed from our systems, please contact our Privacy and Data Protection Officer by email at privacy@stress.com.
Privacy Policy
Contact Us
Contact Us
Quick Links
About Us
News & Media
Careers
Locations
Copyright© 2020 Stress Engineering Services, Inc | Terms & Conditions | Privacy Policy | Sitemap | Site by Upstream Marketing
